Guide to the Darryl Ricardo Matthews Sr. Papers, ca. 1990-2009.
Matthews Sr., Darryl Ricardo Papers,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Darryl Ricardo Matthews Sr. Papers, ca. 1990-2009.
8542
Darryl R. Matthews
10 Cubic Feet.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Papers include Alpha Phi Alpha and National Association of Black Accountants material.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Darryl R. Matthews, Sr., graduated from the University of Central Missouri (1975-1977) with a degree in Sociology/Political Science. He was the Executive Director & Chief Operating Officer of the National Association of Black Accountants (NABA) from March 1998 - March 2007, the 32nd General President of Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity from January 2005 - December 2008, the Executive Director of the National Medical Association (NMA) from October 2011 - January 2014, and the Executive Director of the NABA from January 2014 - October 2015.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Papers include Alpha Phi Alpha and National Association of Black Accountants material.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Matthews, Darryl R.
Subjects:
Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity.; National Association of Black Accountants.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Folder 60 in Box 6 is restricted until 2067 or permission of University Archivist.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Alpha Phi Alpha
Series II. National Association of Black Accountants
CONTAINER LIST
- Alpha Phi Alpha
  - Meetings, Committees, and Official publications, 1996-2008
    - Board of directors meeting, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - Board of directors meeting, 2005-01 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
    - Board of directors meeting, 2006-02 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
    - Board of directors meeting, 2006-06 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Board of directors meeting, 2006-07-25 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Board of directors meeting, 2006-11-10 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Board of directors meeting, 2006-11-11 (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
    - Board of directors meeting, 2007-08 (Box 1, Folder 12-13)
    - Board of directors meeting, 2008-02 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Board of directors meeting, 2008-03 (Box 1, Folder 15-16)
    - Building foundation, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Survey report of the Alpha Phi Alpha headquarters, exterior restoration and repairs, 2001-07 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - National headquarters maintenance committee meeting, 2001-06-15 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Building foundation corporate headquarters site review report, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
    - Fraternity headquarters, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha publications, 1977-07, 1996, 2002, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Era of the Alpha Renaissance, 1995, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Chapter bulletin, 19995-12-1996-08 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - The Sphinx vol. 80-82, 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - The Sphinx vol. 83-85, 1998-2000 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - The Sphinx vol. 87-91, 2001-2006 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - The Sphinx vol. 92-93, 96, 100, 2007-2014 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - The Spirit, 1996, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - The Zeta Omicron Lambda Reporter, 2007-02 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Memorial Project, 2004-2008
    - MLK national memorial project, board of directors meeting, 2004-09-10 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - MLK national memorial project, board of directors meeting, 2005-02-16 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - MLK national memorial project, board of directors meeting, 2005-06-08 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - MLK national memorial project, board of directors meeting, 2005-09-23 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - MLK national memorial project, board of directors meeting, 2005-12-07 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - MLK national memorial project, board of directors meeting, 2006-02-22 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - MLK national memorial project, board of directors meeting, 2006-03-15 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - MLK national memorial project, board of directors meeting, 2006-06-05 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Remarks at the site of the MLK memorial site re-dedication, 2006-07-25 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - MLK national memorial project, board of directors meeting, 2006-09-20 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - MLK national memorial project, board of directors meeting, 2006-12-06 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - MLK national memorial project, board of directors meeting, 2007-02-21 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - MLK national memorial project, board of directors meeting, 2007-03-26 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - MLK national memorial project, board of directors meeting, 2007-06-04 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - MLK national memorial project, board of directors meeting, 2007-08-26 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - MLK national memorial project, board of directors meeting, 2008-03-12 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - MLK national memorial project, board of directors meeting, 2008-06-23 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - MLK national memorial project, board of directors meeting, 2008-09-25 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - MLK national memorial project, board of directors meeting, 2008-12-03 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - MLK national memorial project, executive committee meeting, 2006-08-23 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - MLK national memorial project, executive committee meeting, 2007-05-17 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - MLK national memorial project, executive committee meeting, 2007-08-22 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - MLK national memorial project, executive committee meeting, 2007-11-19 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - MLK national memorial project, executive committee meeting, 2007-12-05 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - MLK national memorial project, executive committee meeting, 2008-02-27 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - MLK national memorial project, executive committee meeting, 2008-05-28 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - MLK national memorial project, executive committee meeting, 2008-08-18 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - MLK national memorial project, executive committee meeting, 2008-11-17 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - MLK national memorial project, memos and correspondence, 1998-2008 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - MLK national memorial project, memos and correspondence, 1999- (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - MLK national memorial project, memos and correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Constitutional convention, 2004-08-05-2004-08-08 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - General convention, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Centennial meeting, 2005-03-23 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Centennial convention, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Centennial convention wrap-up meeting, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - General convention, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 6-7)
    - General convention (legal sized), 2007 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Regional conventions, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - General convention, 2008-07 (Box 3, Folder 9-10)
    - Council of presidents meeting, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
    - Council of presidents meeting, 2006-09-07 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Council of presidents meeting, 2006-09-27 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Council of presidents meeting, 2007-05-18-2007-05-19 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Council of presidents meeting, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Financial review, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Historical financial data, 2004-08 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - General budget data. Houston convention worksheets, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - First quarter fiscal officers meeting, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Mediation or Arbitration, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Public relations materials, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Membership and legal information, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Strategic planning retreat, 2006-05 (Box 3, Folder 24-25)
    - Organizational effectiveness retreat, 2007-12-15 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - 38th Annual Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. memorial breakfast, 2013-01-13 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Ground breaking ceremony, 2006-11-13 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - General Alpha Phi Alpha files, 1995-2009
    - Martin Luther King Day, 2007-01-14 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      African Episcopal Church of St. Thomas, Philadelphia Pennsylvania
    - 23rd Annual MLK Ambassador reception and awards dinner, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - The Dream Concert, program and ticket, 2007-09-18 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Atlanta Dream Dinner program, 2008-06-19 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - 13th MLK breakfast, 2009-01-10 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha / PMDS mail, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha - Pilgrimage to Cornell, 2005-12-19 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Washington Post article on Alpha Phi Alpha, 2006-07-29 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Alphas in Iraq, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Incoming correspondence on hazing/sexuality, 1995, 2005, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Reports and conventions, 1973-2015
    - 67th Anniversary Convention minutes, 1973-08-03-1973-08-09 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 79th Anniversary Convention, 1985-08-09-1985-08-15 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - The Quadrennial Report of Milton C. Davis, 1993-1996 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - 63rd Annual Midwestern Convention, 1995-03 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Executive Director's reports, 1995-1997 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha reports, 1995-08, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - 89th Anniversary Convention minutes, 1995-08-03-1995-08-08 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - 1st Annual Report World Policy Council, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha Policy Council meeting, 1996-01-26 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha programs, 1996-07-12-1996-07-13 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Report of the officers and committees, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - 91st/82nd conventions, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - 55th Western Region convention, 2003-03-13-2003-03-16 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - 97th and 98th convention booklets, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Convention minutes, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Event booklets, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Event booklets, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Event booklets, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Convention reports and souvenir journal, 2005-08 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - The Centenary Report of the Alpha Phi Alpha World Policy Council, 2006-07 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Convention minutes, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - March of Dimes - 2006 Walk America report, 2007-02-09 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha anniversary program, 2007-12-01 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Event booklets, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Convention reports and booklets, 2008-07 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Convention reports and souvenir journal, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Founder's Day celebration, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Convention reports and souvenir journal, 2013-06 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - 67th Western Region Convention, 2015-03-26-2015-03-29 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Eta Lambda Chapter material, 2009,2013 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - SC Chapter of Alpha Phi Alpha, district conference, 2002-10-11-2002-10-13 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Alpha scholarship - registration newsletter, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Membership directory, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Membership handbook, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Strategic planning retreat, 2008-05-17 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Membership directory, 1991 (Box 9)
    - Membership directory, centennial edition, 2006 (Box 9)
  - Darryl Matthews' files, 1965-2015
    - Administrative files, 1969-2008
      - Board of directors meeting, 1999-05 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - South Carolina district conference, 2002-10 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Kappa Phi chapter, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Campaign speech, 2003-03-06 (Box 4, Folder 4)
        Given at the Southern Region convention
      - Tennessee district convention, 2003-11 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Mississippi conference, 2004-01 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Oklahoma district conference, 2004-02- (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - MAAC conference, 2004-02-20 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Western region convention, 2004-03 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Darryl Matthews' Inauguration, 2005-01-08 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Southwest region conference, 2005-03-2005-04 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Birthday card, 2005-02 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Legal correspondence, 2005-02 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, 2002-2005 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Alpha village photographs, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Baltimore master plan, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Statement by Matthews on behalf of the Jenna 6, 2007-09-20 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - CMSU Alumni news, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Self help tips, 1994-03-1995-02 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Notes (handwritten), 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Alpha Phi Alpha Inc. correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - Campaign expenses, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Fax correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - Competitive intelligence, Undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Leadership directory, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - Campaign mailing, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - Lloyd v. Alpha Phi Alpha, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - APA administrative, 1996-2004 (Box 4, Folder 32)
        Includes memberships lists, correspondence, and notes
      - APA administrative, 1995-2001 (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - Email from APA members, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - APA World Policy Council, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - Health Initiative, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - Family news clippings, 1970-2008 (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - Matthews - Awards, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 38)
        High school and the Reserve Officers Training Corps
      - APA administrative, 2003-2005 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 40)
        Letter that includes a dollar bill folded into Matthews' initials.
      - Order of Omega certificate, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - Tidewater, Virginia Meeting, 2004-05 (Box 4, Folder 42)
      - Ohio district convention, 2003-11-2004-03 (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - Notes and debate material, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 44)
        Includes notes, membership lists, and debate materials.
      - Campaign correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - Lupus education foundation, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Membership material, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Member development, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Membership, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Presidential vista, 1996-1999
      - Clinton/Gore advance orientation, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 50)
        Presidential visit
      - Compliance seminar for the advance team, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Chicago diagrams, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Signage for the presidential visit, 1997-11 (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Presidential visit materials, 1997-11 (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - Chicago advance materials, 1997-12 (Box 4, Folder 55)
      - Presidential visit materials, 1997-11 (Box 4, Folder 56)
      - White House visits, 1996-1999 (Box 4, Folder 57)
      - Presidential visit materials, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Correspondence, 1974-2011
      Arranged Chronologically
      - Correspondence, 1974-11-2007 (Box 4, Folder 59)
      - Correspondence, 1979-10-23-2007-10-25 (Box 4, Folder 60)
      - Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 61)
      - Cotman, Ivan Louis letter, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 62)
      - Correspondence, 1996-2009 (Box 4, Folder 63)
      - Davis, Arthur Congressman letter, 2005-01-07 (Box 4, Folder 64)
      - Notes and correspondence, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 65)
      - Texas Bank correspondence, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 66)
      - Pi Eta Kappa chapter thank you card, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - NAACP membership, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 2004-2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 2005-2008 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - APA Correspondence, 2005-09-28-2006-04-24 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - NAACP Columbia, SC Branch, 2005-10 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Congress letter and record, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Letter from President George W. Bush, 2006-04-17 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, 2006-08-2006-12 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Cornell Centennial Celebration - request, 2006-10-26 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence regarding MLK Jr. Monument, 2006-11 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence from Universities, 2006-11, 2008-06 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Sony Pictures "Stomp the Yard" letter, 2006-12-04 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - APA Correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Recommendation letter, 2007-01 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Centennial Celebration, 2006, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Chaka Fattah letter, 2007-01-14 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Army accessions national tour, 2007-03-2007-04 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - National Black MBA Association membership (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Kendrick Meek letter, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Letter from Moss Kendrix, Jr., to Willard Hall with picture of D.R. Matthews, 2008-08-05 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Howard University correspondence, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence with Greek organizations, 2008-06-2008-09 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Government correspondence, 2008-12 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - National Coalition of Black Meeting Planners, 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Letter from Eddie L. Madison, Jr. to Darryl Matthews, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 28)
        Includes newspapers with Eddie's editorials
      - Big Brother Big Sister of America, 2005, 2009-02 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - Invitation to Obama Inauguration, 2009-01-20 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Darryl Matthews invitation to the 5th Pi Eta Kappa Founders Day Induction Ceremony, 2009-05-06 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Keeping African-Americans Political, Political Action Committee (KAP PAC), 2009-10-13 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - MLK National Memorial, commemorative dedication ceremony invitation, 2011-08 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha campaign material, 2004-2008
      - Matthews general president campaign materials, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - DRM nomination, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Presidential papers 1 of 2, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Presidential papers 2 of 2, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Travel and logistics, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Speeches and remarks, 1977-2009
      - Address drafts, Undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Remarks of Darryl R. Matthews, Undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - Friendship Baptist Church address, Undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - Address given at General Convention in Atlanta - Assistant vice president, Midwestern Region, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Milton Davis speech, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - Eastern Region convention, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - Founders Day address, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - Address at Eastern Regional Convention, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 46)
      - Phi Nu Omega Chapter AKA, Inc. - 3rd annual breast cancer awareness luncheon, 2005-10-30 (Box 5, Folder 47)
      - Welcoming remarks for strategic planning retreat, 2006-05-05-2006-05-07 (Box 5, Folder 48)
      - Mens Day Address, 2007-02-11 (Box 5, Folder 49)
      - Address to Choppin Church, 2007-02-11 (Box 5, Folder 50)
      - Martin Luther King Jr. address, 2007-05-05, 2009-01-10 (Box 5, Folder 51)
      - Freedom Fund dinner speech, 2007-10-25 (Box 5, Folder 52)
      - Remarks of Darryl R. Matthews, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 53)
      - Remarks of Darryl R. Matthews, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 54)
      - Matthews speeches, 2005, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Matthews speeches, 2008-07-20 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - General Darryl Matthews files, 1965-2015
      - Signed photographs - Kenny Lattimore & Chante Moore, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Various notes (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Notes (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Department of the Army Field Manual, Military Leadership, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Becoming a winner article, 1979, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Prince Hall Freemasons Journal, 1987-03-1999-08 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Bingwa, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Doctorate of Hamburgerology, 1999-07-13 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Photographs, 2000-2009 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Edward W. Brook Courthouse dedication, 2000-06-20 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Fullwood Foundation, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - William H. Myers memorial service, 2003-06-11 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Calendar, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Freedom's Song, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Association for the Study of African American Life and History, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - St. Timothy's Parish Day School Multicultural Day, 2006-02-23 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Congressional Record: Tribute to Black History Month, 2006-02-28 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - African Americans of Distinction Legacy Awards program, 2006-10-20 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Photograph - Black Enterprise cover, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Nouveau Riche University, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Urban Ed, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Converse lawsuit, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Converse agreement, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - National African American History Month presidential proclamation & photo, 2007-02-12 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - CDC AIDS Crisis, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - High Museum Art, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Medgar Evers induction ceremony, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Celebration for Alfred Carver Bailey, 2008-07-21 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Tuskegee Airmen National Historic Site Grand Opening, 2008-10 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - Beyond This Place photo book, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - Nickia McMurtrey, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - John Hope Franklin, 2009-06-11 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Congressional Gold Medal Ceremony in honor of Edward William Brooke, 2009-10-28 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      - Thank You Dekalb, Census 2010 photo, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - Edward W. Brook service materials, 2015-03 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - Emily D. Blanton memorial service, 2015-09-15 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      - Benny J. Primm memorial service, 2015-10-21 (Box 6, Folder 37)
      - Calendars, 1996-2008 (Box 10)
      - Certificates and recognitions, 1987-2011 (Box 10)
      - Photo book - Edward Brooke Luncheon, Undated (Box 10)
      - Photo book - MLK memorial, 2011 year in review, 2011 (Box 10)
    - Other Greek Organizations, 1996-2008
      - Matthews Certificate of Membership, Undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
      - Good Scout Award - Darryl Matthews, 1996-11-04 (Box 6, Folder 39)
      - National Pan-Hellenic Founder's Day, 1997-05-18 (Box 6, Folder 40)
      - Gamma Chi Lambda Chapter 50th anniversary, 1997-09-21 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      - National Pan-Hellenic Council budget & finance report, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      - National Pan-Hellenic Council handbook, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 43)
      - National Pan-Hellenic Council, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 46)
      - Grand Masters, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 47)
      - John H. Johnson essay contest, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 48)
      - Coalition Assessment project, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 50)
      - Organizational consultant proposal, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 51)
      - No more "N-word", 2007 (Box 6, Folder 53)
      - Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 54)
      - National Pan-Hellenic Council Materials, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 55)
      - National Pan-Hellenic Council Constitution & By-laws revisions and Restructuring Task Force Report, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 56)
      - Belford vs. Lawson oratorical, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 57)
      - Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority invitations, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 58)
      - Wesley Brown dedication dinner, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Other publications, 1970-2013
      - Jet Magazine, 1970-04-01 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Jet Magazine, 1995-09-18-2006-11-27 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Black Enterprise Magazine, 1982-04-2008-11 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Crescent, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Newspapers, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - National Black Monitor newspaper, 1996-06 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Newspapers, 1997-11-1997-12 (Box 7, Folder 7)